(Stuart:)I, um-- I want you to know that
even though we're on opposite sides...
(Stuart:)...I bear you no ill will.
(Penny:)-Thank you, Stuart. It's nice to know.
-Mm-hm.
(Stuart:)People from opposite sides
often have good relationships.
(Stuart:)You know, Romeo and Juliet...
(Stuart:)...Tony and Maria from West Side Story.
(Stuart:)What's-his-name
and the big, blue chick in Avatar.
(Stuart:)I'm gonna bowl now.
(Sheldon:)Be the ball, Howard.
(Howard:)Leave me alone, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You weren't the ball.
(Penny:)Hey, thanks.
(Leonard:)-This is fun, huh?
-Yeah.
It's good we got out
and did something physical.
(Penny:)-Mm-hm.
-Gets us out of our heads.
(Leonard:)You get in your head...
(Leonard:)...you start to over-think, over-analyze,
obsess, you worry.